eteligis.com 2013-09-30

# eTeligis Privacy Details

Eteligis is committed to providing its online users with services and information in an efficient and secure manner. This privacy policy explains what personal information is collected on Eteligis.com from users of Eteligis' various online services, how that information is used and what measures Eteligis takes to safeguard its users' privacy.

 **What personal information is collected on Eteligis.com?**

There is no general registration requirement for users of Eteligis.com. Instead, we only collect information as needed to provide you with particular services such as submitting releases, requested targeted news feeds, requested marketing information, and requested hosted online newsroom e-mail news alerts. Depending on the service for which you register, we may collect some or all of the following information: name, title, company name, e-mail address, street address, telephone and facsimile numbers, employer company profile, client profile, beat (for media users) and categories of interest.

 **How does Eteligis use the information collected on Eteligis.com?**

Information about individual users collected on Eteligis.com is used for internal business purposes, including customizing services, contacting members regarding orders and responding to requests for information. On occasion, Eteligis or one of its members or affiliates may also use this information to inform you of news, service upgrades or marketing information that may be of particular interest to you.

In addition, Eteligis tracks anonymous user data to provide information and reports regarding usage of the website and press release activity to members, affiliates, advertisers and for other lawful purposes.

 **Does Eteligis provide personal information collected on Eteligis.com to third parties?**

Eteligis does not sell, trade or rent personal information collected online and will not knowingly disclose any individual personal information to third parties except as follows:

(1) In order to provide you with requested services, Eteligis may provide contact or other necessary information to affiliated companies to complete your service request; (2) If you register to have press releases or other information for a particular Eteligis member's company in an Eteligis-hosted online newsroom electronically delivered to you the member company may be notified that you have utilized one of these services and provided with your e-mail address, mobile number or other platform-specific contact information in order to follow-up and provide you with additional information; (3) When disclosure is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be causing injury to or interference with the rights (including property rights) or safety of other users or third parties or of Eteligis; and (4) When Eteligis reasonably believes that disclosure is required by law or to comply with legal process served on Eteligis.

 **Participation in Business Wire SMS Alert Services [OPTIONAL]**

Participation in our SMS Service is free of charge but standard carrier text messaging charges will apply. You may change your mind at any time by following the opt-out instructions below. You represent that you are the owner or authorized user of the wireless device you use to sign up for the SMS Service, and that you are authorized to approve the applicable charges. You acknowledge and agree that the SMS Service is provided via wireless systems to transmit communications over complex networks. We do not guarantee that your use of the SMS Service will be private or secure, and we are not liable to you for any lack of privacy or security you may experience. You are fully responsible for taking precautions and providing security measures best suited for your situation and intended use of the SMS Service.

You may unsubscribe from alerts for a particular company [here](http://www.eteligis.com/contact.aspx).

 **How can I change or update the information I provide on Eteligis.com?**

Where user profile information is collected and stored in order to provide you with requested services, Eteligis offers you the opportunity to change or update your profile information at any time. Depending on the service you wish to update, you may change your data by visiting the "My Profile" section of Eteligis.com. For alert notifications, you may click the "unsubscribe" button on email alerts or follow the SMS unsubscribe prompts from your mobile device.

 **Does Eteligis.com use cookies or similar tools?**

Yes, however, Eteligis only uses cookies to facilitate functions at the Eteligis websites and does not record or store any information about your movements on the Internet outside the Eteligis websites.

Eteligis.com also uses services provided by the News Registry. The News Registry collects content usage information and may use cookies in conjunction with this activity. Your continued readership of the Site means you accept the privacy policy of the News Registry. Please refer to the News Registry privacy policy at http://www.newsregistry.com/privacycenter/servicepolicy.aspx   for further information.

In addition, Eteligis.com uses web beacons. Web beacons are used to understand website traffic patterns and the number of visitors to our website or other sites containing news distributed by Eteligis and to collect aggregate data reported to clients in measurement reports in order to measure the effectiveness of their press releases.

Please note that if you click on a link to a third-party website from Eteligis.com, the linked-to site may have different policies and practices with regard to cookies and Eteligis has no control over and is not responsible for such policies or practices. You should always consult the privacy policy governing any web site you visit on the internet for complete information about their policies and practices.

 **What security measures does Eteligis take to safeguard its online users' privacy?**

Information you submit at Eteligis.com upon registration for specific services is password-protected so that the only parties who have access to the information besides Eteligis and its agents and affiliates are the member entity and its employees. In addition, individual employees of members will receive individual passwords when they log-on to submit press releases online, and information submitted using Eteligis.com is further protected by Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software, which encrypts the information during transmission.

In order to protect the integrity of the password system, members should refrain from disclosing passwords and immediately change any passwords that may have been compromised.

Eteligis will never ask you for your password by e-mail, so members and their employees should not respond to unsolicited e-mail requests asking for password information even if such requests appear to be from Eteligis.

Please be advised that no data transmission over the internet is 100% secured. Eteligis is committed to protecting users' personal information, but cannot guarantee or warrant the security of this information when it is sent to or through Eteligis.com. Transmission of such information is therefore at the risk of the user.

 **Usernames and Passwords**

Users may register via Eteligis.com. Once usernames and passwords (the "Login Information") are issued to users (the "Authorized Users"), the Authorized Users accept full responsibility for the use of the Login Information. The Authorized User may not, under any circumstances, release their Login Information to any other person for any reason, and is required to keep the Login Information strictly confidential. If any breach of security, theft or loss, or unauthorized disclosure of the Login Information occurs, the Authorized User must immediately notify Eteligis of such security breach.

 **Privacy policy updates**

This policy will be updated from time to time as necessary to address new or modified services and functions. Eteligis will provide you with notice of any changes or updates to this policy at the home page of Eteligis.com.
